Hello friends, today we will talk about the general
insurance company ICC Lombard.
Today, ICC Lombard's shares have seen a sharp
decline. Its shares have been dealt a
major blow by a tax notice. The
Director and General of GST Intelligence has
sent a notice to ICC Lombard General Insurance to recover dues of approximately ₹1,730 crore between July 2017 and March 2022, the company informed the exchange.
According to the information provided by the company in the exchange filing, the
income tax notice received regarding GST dues is
related to insurance premium and insurance commission. The company said that this is
related to notification matters, regarding which it will
send a response within the stipulated time, as per the industry. The
company has been sent a notice
from the GCI unit for tax dues of approximately ₹1,730 crore under Section 73 of the Central Goods and Services Tax
2017.
ICC Lombard
received the tax notice on September 27, two days after the appointment of the new MD and CEO Sanjeev Mantri. This is the second time in two months
that the company has received a tax-related
notice, having received it on 8 previous occasions.  Giving
information to the exchange about working on August 1, it was
asked to make a tax of Rs 273.44 crore through Income Tax GST. This matter was
related to Solved Adjusted Per GST and Input Tax Credit of Motor Clamper Settled. The company had
also deposited this amount without accepting it. The
company said that it will file its reply when
today. In a time when ICC Lombard is
seeing a decline, the
company